emeditor.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy – EmEditor (Text Editor)

## Emurasoft Privacy Policy Notice

All Emurasoft, Inc. products and services are governed by our privacy policy, which explains how we treat personal information.

Our Commitment to Privacy: Emurasoft’s privacy policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Emurasoft. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Emurasoft, and we go to great lengths to protect it. We never share your information with anyone else, for any reason.

The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Emurasoft website (*.emeditor.com).

 _Account Information._ You can order products, make requests, and register to access the forums. “Personal information” is information that you provide to us which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: name, address, email address, and phone number.

 _Profile Information and User Contributions._ You may create a public profile to share personal information or make user contributions. When you leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also your Internet Protocol (IP) address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

 _Contact Form._ We may collect personal information through your communications via our contact form. We keep contact form submissions for customer service purposes, but we do not use the information submitted through the contact form for marketing purposes. Please ensure that no sensitive personal data is submitted in connection with your requests for customer support (for example, credit card numbers, etc.).

 _Embedded content from other websites._ Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content.

 _Cookies and Other Technology._ A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preference. When you visit our website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser, however cookies do not identify any individual user.

The Way We Use Information: We use the information you provide about yourself or others when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not stored or shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to access the forums. Information you submit on the forum registration pages is used only for the purpose of using the forums, unless you specify otherwise. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the purposes described when the information is provided, unless you specify otherwise.

Emurasoft’s default option is to opt-in, meaning that Emurasoft will never send you newsletters or any other marketing emails unless you initiate the process to receive those emails. For example, you will not receive newsletters just because you have purchased products from us. You will only receive newsletters if you sign up for them on the newsletters registration page.

Our Commitment to Data Security: To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy: Protecting the privacy of children is important. Our sites are not aimed to attract children and their objectives are not to collect personal information from children. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our websites from those we know are under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

How You Can Access, Correct, or Update Your Information: If you register on our website, you can see, edit, or delete your personal information at any time. Website administrators can also see and edit that information. You can also access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us at [info@emurasoft.com](mailto:info@emurasoft.com) and requesting the information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

Users’ Choices: We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

Changes to the Privacy Policy: Emurasoft may update and amend this privacy statement from time-to-time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site and by updating the “Last Modified Date” at the bottom of this privacy statement.

How to Contact Us: Should you have any questions or concerns about these privacy policies, or if you feel your privacy inquiry or request has not been addressed to your satisfaction, please send us an email at [info@emurasoft.com](mailto:info@emurasoft.com).

Last Modified: May 25, 2018
